There are at least as many ways to set up
设置编程环境的方式
a programming environment as there are programmers,
比程序员的数量还多
and there's no right or wrong way to go about it.
没有什么方式是绝对正确或错误
However, if you're just starting out in writing
然而 如果你才刚刚开始写 Python
Python you might like to see my screen to get some ideas.
你可能会想看看我的屏幕来获得一些灵感
Time for a tour of my screen.
浏览我屏幕的时间到了
Over here, I have my text editor.
这里是我的文本编辑器
I'm using sublime text which is great for getting started,
我用的是 Sublime Text 它非常适合初学者
but my fellow Udacians recommended a notepad++,
但是优达学城的其他同事也推荐 Notepad++、
atom, vim and many others.
Atom、Vim 或者其他的编辑器
A text editor is really different from a word processor, so don't mix them up.
文本编辑器和文字处理软件 (如 Word) 大有不同 别弄混淆了
Code needs to be written line by line,
代码需要一行一行地编写
with line breaks and indentations included on purpose
根据目的添加换行或缩进
and ways that fundamentally change how the code is read and run.
从根本上影响着代码读取和运行方式
Good text editors have
好的文本编辑器
simple but vital features such as syntax highlighting and line numbers.
拥有简单但至关重要的特性 比如语法高亮和显示行数
Editors are highly customizable to suit your style.
编辑器可以根据你的风格进行高度定制
One setting that I use on coding in Python
我编写 Python 时的一个设定是
is the setting that converts tabs into four spaces.
将 Tab 转化为四个空格
Indentation levels in Python are always multiples of
在 Python 中 缩进级别通常是
four spaces and I don't want to be making mistakes as I hit the spacebar.
四个空格的倍数 而且我不想在敲击空格键时出错
The tabs shortcut really helps.
Tab 的快捷方式真的很有帮助
The text editor isn't the only thing on my screen right now.
现在我屏幕上 不仅仅只有文本编辑器
The terminal window is here so that I can run my script.
命令行窗口也在这里 用来运行我的脚本
Generally, I can't write a whole lot of code in one go
通常而言 我不能在一次运行中写很多代码
because something will go wrong and I'll need to find the issue and debug it.
因为出现错误的时候 我需要找到问题并调试
When there is an error it will show up here,
当有错误的时候它会出现在
in the terminal for me to read.
命令行窗口来供我阅读
I make small changes to the code in the text editor,
我在文本编辑器的代码中做一些小改动
then run the script to see the output.
然后运行脚本查看输出
If I see a problem I'll try to fix it or if things seem to be working, I'll move on.
如果看到问题 我就尝试修复 或者如果一切正常 我就会继续
I've also got the Udacity classroom and some documentation open in my browser.
另外我还在浏览器中打开了 Udacity 教室和一些文档
Normally, I'll need a browser open to look up
通常 我会需要打开浏览器来查看文档
documentation or to search for the solution to a bug I encounter along the way.
或者搜索在编码中遇到 bug 的解决方案